Guide to the Frank J. Taylor Papers, 1928-1967
Department of Special Collections
- BOOKS: BRO. CASTLE & BRO. COOKE
  - Hawaii--More Research Material (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Hawaii Statehood--Research Material (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Hawaii--Pictures (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Research Material on a planned but never published handbook on how to be a widow (i.e., manage your husband's estate after his death) (Box 12, Folder 11)
Frank J. Taylor Additional Materials
- Drawer A. Reader's Digest Correspondence. (Box 17, 18)
  - 1. 1940 - 1949.
  - 2. 1950 - 1953.
  - 3. 1954.
  - 4. 1955.
  - 5. 1956.
  - 6. 1957.
  - 7. 1958.
  - 8. Writer scouting assignment; Paul Palmer correspondence- 1958.
  - 9. Correspondence with writers.
  - 10. 1958 - 1961, memos to Paul Palmer about writers.
  - 11. 1959 - 1960, letters from editors.
  - 12. Paul Palmer correspondence about scouting for writers, 1959.
  - 13. Correspondence with writers, 1959.
  - 14. 1959.
  - 15. Paul Palmer correspondence re writers and article ideas, 1960.
  - 16. 1960.
  - 17. Letters from Paul Palmer to writers re manuscript and ideas for articles, 1958 - 1962.
  - 18. Correspondence about writers, 1960.
  - 19. Correspondence with Paul Palmer and other Reader's Digest editors, 1961.
  - 20. Correspondence with writers, 1961.
  - 21. Correspondence with Reader's Digest editors, 1962.
  - 22. 1963.
  - 23. 1964.
  - 24. 1965.
  - 25. 1966.
  - 26. 1967.
- Drawer B. Correspondence. (Box 17, 18)
  - 1. Saturday Evening Post, 1941 - 1947.
  - 2. Saturday Evening Post, 1948 - 1951.
  - 3. Saturday Evening Post, 1952.
  - 4. Saturday Evening Post, 1953.
  - 5. Saturday Evening Post, 1954.
  - 6. Saturday Evening Post, 1955.
  - 7. Saturday Evening Post, 1956.
  - 8. Saturday Evening Post, 1957.
  - 9. Saturday Evening Post, 1958.
  - 10. Saturday Evening Post, 1959.
  - 11. Saturday Evening Post, 1960.
  - 12. Saturday Evening Post, 1961.
  - 13. Saturday Evening Post, 1962.
  - 14. Country Gentleman editors.
  - 15. Collier's editors.
  - 16. Willis Kingsley Wing, literary agent, 1932 - 1935.
  - 17. Carl Brandt, Sr., literary agent, 1941 - 1948.
  - 18. Carl Brandt, Sr., literary agent, 1949 - 1953.
- Drawer C. Correspondence, re: (Box [19?])
  - 1. Doubleday and Co., Inc., 1949 - 1950.
  - 2. Holiday.
  - 3. Little, Brown, and Co., Our USA - A Gay Geography
  - 4. McGraw-Hill - High Horizons - A History of United Airlines.
  - 5. McGraw-Hill Book Co., Inc.
  - 6. McGraw-Hill Book Co., Inc. - Union Oil correspondence.
  - 7. McGraw-Hill Book Co., Inc. - Southern Pacific correspondence.
  - 8. This Week.
  - 9. V.I.P. correspondence, incl.:
    - Harry Truman
    - Herbert Hoover
      (incl. memo of interview given by HH on 3/31/33)
    - Erle Stanley Gardner
    - Walter Dilli gham
    - Roy Howard
    - G. C. Marshall, Jr. (when he was a.d.c. to Gen. Pershing, 1922)
    - Nelson Rockefellar (when he was with the Dept. of State, 1943)
    - Laurance Rockefellar
- Drawer D. Miscellaneous correspondence in alphabetical sequence, A - Z, plus two folders of fan mail at the back of the drawer. (Box 20)